[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "VBZ", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Is this going to come to praying again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "Well, praying does help.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "(voice over): And remember this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", ":", "CC", "NN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "I have been unfaithful to my wife.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "It is a negative thing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "I don't find it negative at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Do I really anger you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Yes, because I think it is a deliberately provocative stance that you take.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "I don't know if you have seen the \"Book of Mormon\" of Matt Stone and Trey Parker?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt Stone", "Trey Parker"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Well, let me ask you, how did we get here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "I believe in this superior being, a God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Why do you need to label that as something that is God or something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Because I have never heard an atheist explain to me --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "And what happens at the end of our lives?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Well, the answer to saying we can't understand it, is not an answer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "So how do you think that we got here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "What do you think happens when you die?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Where do you go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Where do you go, I mean when you die.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "You must be terrified of death?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1890"]}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "But what do you think happens to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "How scared are you of 1890.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "1890?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "1890, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "You weren't alive then, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "Is that a horror to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "So why is 2090 any worse than that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBZ", "CD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "I'm not horrified by any sort of dying, because I believe you go on to a celestial place which is wonderful.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2090"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Where is your evidence of the celestial place?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Because I come back to the issue of creation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Aren't those the same answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "You cannot write a book basically telling a bunch of people around the world, billions of people, who believe in God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "We are all a bit crazy though, a bit nuts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Thor"]}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "Thor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "Yeah, Thor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Because it is not the same thing and you know it, and you are being deliberately perverse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "OK, OK, so you are saying that all the Muslim God, the God of Hindu, the Gods of God of Catholics and Protestants are all the same God, even though there are different rules?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "ORGAN: No, but I have an respect for anybody from any religion that has a spiritual and religious conviction and belief in a godlike entity in their lives.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["God of Hindu", "Gods of God of Catholics"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Tough to comfort them in this terrible time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "I don't think that to comfort them I lie to them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "And you have never touched alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "I believe touching it might be wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "But you don't drink alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "I don't drink alcohol, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "You don't do drugs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "I don't do-drink caffeine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "You don't fornicate with ladies of the night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "No, although my wife exists during the night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "You don't gamble?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "I have-when I say I haven't drank, I really mean it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "And why would you live in Las Vegas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Because there is nothing I like doing more than I like than my show.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Las Vegas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "VBZ", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "It is going to come to praying again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Well, praying does help.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "What is the answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "I always seem to think that the most important thing is individuals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "It is why you vote people, and why they get elected, it is why they run for office?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "I am not sure that is exactly the way I see it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Is the solution to give them government money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "I think that the solution is probably to do a little bit of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "So you think that raising-not on the small business people would do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "You have to get the revenues from the higher owners, in my view.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Yes, and I assume that you are helping them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Well, I'm talking about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "But you are also giving them money and so on, I assume?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "I do give money.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "They do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "JJ"], "qSentId": 350, "question": "You don't think you can help people directly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "I think most people-", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I think, you know, you've got Kiva (ph), doing these microloans all over the world that are making huge changes without any government force, at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "What is the one thing you would do, if you were president, to get Americans back to work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "NNPS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "What I would do is I think make the government much, much smaller.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Just to shut me up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "ORGAN: When we come back, I want to talk you about magic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Your two kids are called Zolten Penn and a Moxie Crime Fighter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Yes, my son's name is my wife's maiden name.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Penn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Coke"], "LOCATION": ["Maine"]}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "CD", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Moxie Crime Fighter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Moxie, this is one -- Moxie, as you may not know, not being from our wonderful country, Moxie is the beverage, it is an American brand name out of Maine, called Moxie, that then went into -- it is one of the odd brand names that went into the dictionary, not as like Coke meaning soda, but rather as meaning guts, gumption, and so on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Is she old enough to realize what you have done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "No, no, it is better than that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Does it feel like a marriage to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "You like him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "There was no sort of cuddly feeling for him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "How do you get along now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Wonderfully.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Do you socialize away from work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "ILLETTE: About twice a year, we go out socially together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Do you do all of the talking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PDT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "No, no, no, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "So he's perfectly garrulous when you have dinner and stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "More so than me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "What would you pray for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "I would pray for, I think, more perfect knowledge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Why was it surprising?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "What would you hope to gain from this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "I can't hammer nails for the rest of my life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "``", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "''", "CC", "DT", "``", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "''", ",", "CC", "DT", "``", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "''", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "When you have seen what has happened to America and you have seen the emergence of the Tea Party as a proper formidable political force, do you feel a twinge of regret that you are not at the forefront of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "You know, I don't think that there is a lot to gained by the \"might have been\" or the \"would have been\", or the \"could have beens\" of life.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "The super rich who are paying a disproportionate sum of taxes in their total tax threshold, compared to the guy compared on the street?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "I would say I absolutely believe in the notion of tax reform.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Which of the Republicans, at the moment-and we are seeing a clear pattern beginning to emerge with Romney, and Bachmann and Perry and so on-who do you think fundamentally has what it takes in the overall package to seriously challenge Barack Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "I think that the primary system will winnow that out.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney", "Bachmann", "Perry", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Well, you are trying to get me to pick a horse and I don't want to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Well, I'm saying you are in the paddock.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Could you see him rallying to the cause of the party, if no one has emerged by then that people think could beat Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Well, I think there is talk of that still happening.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "So is Michele Bachmann the one in that case, is she the obvious person now beginning to capture enough of the public's imagination to potentially be that person?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "No, I don't think you could look at it that simplistically.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michele Bachmann"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "But of those names, of the three, you know, which one if you had to put one in the race tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WDT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "ANFORD: I'm not going to pick a horse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "How does it feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "It is humbling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Given that, do you feel great regret, or is that the wrong emotion to put to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "Well, I think that, you -- I mean, anybody who has been married doesn't start out the beginning thinking, boy, I hope some day I get divorced and I hope some day that the train comes off of the track.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "And what have you learned about yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "Well, I have learned a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "How has the public been with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "They're incredible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "How did that make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "It was fabulous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "What would you do differently?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "A whole host of things, none of which are particularly productive in terms of my boys who might be watching the show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "Would anything really have made much difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "Yeah, I'd say a couple different things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Having got it wrong in your marriage, do you feel like you've learned enough from that whole experience, and the bruising exposure and scandal to get it right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "I hope so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "Are you happier in yourself now do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "It's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "Do you have any plans to remarry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "We'll see.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "Would it be a nice ending to the saga for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 727, "question": "It wouldn't be the most shocking thing we'd read or hear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 728, "answer": "We'll see.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]